# Camila Sánchez Ramos

## Tier l Support Specialist

Experience in QA and customer support. Passion for building accessible & responsive code, matched by keen eye for design and attention to detail. Creative problem-solver and motivated team player.

Open to in-office, hybrid, and remote positions.

### **Experience**

#### **Tier 1 Support Specialist**

2022-Present

The Support Heroes

- Provide Technical First-Level Support for Shopify App developers.
- Answering tickets via email, providing quality support aligned with the goals and values of the company.

#### **Quality Inspector**

2021-2022

Colombina Conservas

- Analysis of the quality of the finished product.
- Inspection of raw materials.
- Analysis of the prefabricated product.

### Selected Projects

#### Sunday23!

2023

HTML | CSS | JavaScript

This is a daily, weekly or monthly planner to organize your tasks, customize your workflow to increase efficiency and productivity.

### **Contact**

+57 3153412090

sanchezramoscamila@gmail.com

www.camilasanchez.com

github.com/CamilaS25

### **Education**

# The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp

Udemy 2023

### **Industrial Chemistry**

Universidad Tecnológica de Pereira 2016-2021

### **Skills**

#### **Technical**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript

#### Transferable:

- Customer Service
- Problem-Solving
- Creative
- Detail-Oriented
- Time Management
- Analytical